

About Me

I am a passion driven, experienced and suitably qualified developer with a thorough knowledge of software development, maintain software and web design. I am a hard worker, sincere and have team work spirit. I am energetic, creative and also versatile; I have worked with different companies with extensive experience in Information Technology.

MUPENZI Theogene

Professional Experience

LYCEE DE NYANZA | Trainer

Web developer

January, 2023 - Current

Key responsibilities:

- Trainer in software development
- · Lab technician

IBB TSS | Trainer

September, 2022 - January, 2023

Key responsibilities:

- Trainer in software development
- · Lab technician

AMBC Ltd. | Services operator

March, 2022 – July, 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Provide online services to the clients
- Graphic design (logo, Invitation cards, banners...)
- Maintenance of company's devices as well as Clients' devices

VISION SACCO GATORE | Internee

August, 2021 - November, 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Cameras installation and monitoring
- Network troubleshooting
- Data management

Projects

- INKAYANJYE mobile app
- Academic monitor
- Covid vaccination Booking system (CVBS)
- Library Management System
- Sacco Transactions System

Achievements

Best performer of IPRC Huye at college May, 2022 level on RP 5th Graduation

React/Redux certificate offered by 2022

Sololearn.com

2019 Got Code and design Certificate from

GIZ and RISA

My Contact

mupenzi17theo@gmail.com

+250 789 564 776

Kigali, Rwanda

mupenzil7.github.io

Programming Skill

- Python-Flask
- NodeJS
- PostGreSQL database
- PHP Laravel
- ReactJS/Redux
- Vue.is
- · IOT and Cloud computing
- · Mysql database
- · Java programming
- JavaScript

Education Background

RP-IPRC HUYE

Advanced diploma(A1) in Information and Communication Technology

Completed in 2021

KIGARAMA TSS

Diploma(A2) in Computer Science

Completed in 2015

Languages

kinyarwanda





